# Hela Abeda

#### **FullStack JS Web Developer**

abadahela@gmail.com

https://helabedaporfolio.vercel.app +216 21 593 065

#### **ABOUT**

"Holding a degree in Electrical Engineering, specializing in Embedded Electronics and Telecommunications, I am versatile and autonomous in my role while enjoying working in a team. With 2 years of experience, I have specialized in Full Stack JS development and website creation, although I am also capable of website deployment and web design. I am currently seeking new opportunities."

#### **SOCIAL NETWORKS**

in@hela-abada-b0b560120/

**₽**@helabeda

#### **EDUCATION AND TRAINING**

Full-Stack Javascript Bootcamp Certificate, GO MY CODE

From May 2021 to October 2021

Gafsa, Tunisie

**Java Certificate, Electroworks** 

From January 2021 to March 2021

Gafsa, Tunisie

National Engineering Diploma, ESPRIMS - Private Superior School of Engineers

From September 2015 to July 2018

Specialization: Embedded Electronics and Telecommunications

Monastir, Tunisie

## **Bachelor's Degree in Electrical Engineering,**

#### **Higher Institute of Technological Studies**

Specialization: Industrial Electricity.

## From September 2012 to June 2015

Gafsa, Tunisie

#### **EXPÉRIENCES PROFESSIONNELLES**

## Front-End Developer, Satoripop

From April 2023 to September 2023

Sousse, tunisia

- Developed and implemented responsive web designs for <u>Carrefour.tn</u> and <u>Veamly.com</u>, resulting in an enhanced user experience and increased customer engagement.
- Resolved complex technical issues and bugs, ensuring smooth website performance and minimizing downtime.
- Performed maintenance, improvements, and integrated new modules, such as Magento, on the website, while also resolving any related bugs.
- Implemented SEO best practices, leading to higher search engine rankings and increased organic traffic to the websites.
- Optimized website performance by applying best practices in front-end development, resulting in faster page load times and improved SEO rankings.
- Contributed to the development and maintenance of the Content Management System (CMS), streamlining content updates and enhancing website management.

<u>Utilized technologies such as:</u> ReactJs, GraphQL, Magento2, Venia, TailwindCss, Starpi, AstroJs, JavaScript and TypeScript.

#### **EXPÉRIENCES PROFESSIONNELLES**

## FullStack developer, Highway

Since July 2022

Tunis, Tunisie

- Creating MERN stack applications.
- Backend (NodeJS) and frontend (ReactJS) development of the website for the startup International Highway.
- Maintenance, improvement, addition of new modules to the site, and bug fixes.
- Development of the site and its responsive version.
- Working with Figma for designing web and mobile applications.
- Orchestration of application deployment with continuous deployment tools.
   <u>Utilized technologies such as:</u> ReactJs, NodeJs, ExpressJs, MongoDB, Redux, Bootstrap, Material UI and JavaScript.

#### **FullStack Web Developer, Freelance**

Since November 2021

- Creation of MERN stack applications.
- Creation of RESTful services with Node.js.
- Programmation des codes responsives.
- Creation of e-commerce sites.

## **Electrical Engineer, Electrical Works for Industrial Building TEBI**

From August 2020 to December 2020 Tunis, Tunisie

### Adjunct Professor, Higher Institute of Technological Studies ISET

From September 2019 to July 2020

Gafsa, Tunisie

- Sensor Course.
- Measurement and Metrology Course.
- Computer-Aided Design (CAD) Practical Work (using ISIS, ARES, and designing electronic cards).

## **LANGUAGES**

Arabic French

**English** 

#### **COMPÉTENCES**

React.Js Starpi
AstroJs GraphQL
Figma Tailwind
Express.js Redux
Material-UI Bootstrap
HTML 5 Scrum/Agile

java CSS3
JavaScript / ES6 Angular
Trello Magento2
API / RestAPI Node.js
MongoDB/ Mongoose TypeScript

Git, GitHub, GitLab

#### **ASSETS**

Time Management Skills

Adaptability and Flexibility

Excellent Communication Skills

Leadership Skills

Technical Expertise

Strong Problem-Solving Skills